https://www.commbank.com.au/support/privacy.html?ei=CB-footer_privacy

Help & support
CommBank Search. Dialog start.
Privacy policy
Protecting your information and being clear about what we do with it is a vital part of our relationship with you.
You and your privacy
In our increasingly digital world, we take our responsibility to protect your privacy very seriously by applying strict security and privacy controls to the way we handle your personal information. We use the information you provide us to give you the best possible banking experiences, to help us assess your applications as well as design and tailor products and services so they’re just right for you.
Our privacy policy
We value your trust and aim to be transparent about how we handle your personal information. Our Privacy Policy covers:
Information about the CommBank Group
What information we collect about you
How we use your information
Who we share your information with
Credit checks and credit reporting
How we keep your information safe
How you can access, update and correct your information
How to make a privacy complaint
How to contact us and find out more.
Our Privacy Policy applies to the handling of your personal information by our Australian businesses. A few of those have their own policies - see section 5 of our policy for more information.
Sometimes we update our Privacy Policy. You can always find the most up-to-date version on this page. Download a PDF version of our Privacy Policy. If you have any questions, contact us.
We can help
Security and privacy
Contact us
Find your nearest branch
Commonwealth Bank
